volcanoecigs.com 2015-04-19

# Privacy Policy

Volcanoecigs.com understands that your privacy while using our Site is important, especially when conducting business or providing sensitive personal information. This Notice will govern our Privacy Policy for users of this Site, whether or not a transaction of any sort is conducted while visiting.

### Your Personal Information

The information we collect from customers helps us to personalize our site to you and continually improve our customer service pursuit. The following is some of the information that we gather about our users.

**Information You Provide Us:** When you create a user account on-line or communicate with us via e-mail, letter, fax or phone, we receive and store the information that you have provided. This information is basic, including: name, address, phone, fax and cell phone numbers, e-mail address and business information (if applicable). We use this information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, communicating with you and customizing future shopping for you. **** ****  
 ****

**Third Party Vendors:** In addition to collecting your information, we have third party vendors who will also collect your information in order to provide the products and/or services you've requested (e.g. credit card companies, fulfillment companies, call centers, marketing companies and freight companies). In general, these companies are intermediaries acting solely to provide services related to your request. Most of these vendors have their own privacy policy to protect your information, and have access to personal information needed to perform their functions on behalf of Volcanoecigs.com, but may not use the same for other purposes. **** ****  
 ****

**Are Cookies Used On The Volcanoecigs.com Site:** We use cookies to obtain a variety of information which provides us details as to what product and information our visitors view the most. Cookies can also be used to protect your information. If you wish to disable our cookies from obtaining this information, you can privatize your browser or seek programs that will allow you to visit our site anonymously without losing most of the site's functionality.

### Does Volcanoecigs.com Share the Information It Receives?

Under no circumstances will we ever give away or sell your personal information to anyone else for any reason whatsoever, without prior written approval from yourself. Any information we gain through our use of customer polls, surveys, cookies, session tracking or anything else, is used internally and for the sole purpose of providing you better service. If you are on our mailing list and you ask us to remove you, we will do so immediately and will not attempt to sell your information. As we do with our own, we respect your privacy. Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and we are not in the business of selling it to other companies.

### How Secure Is Information About Me?

All of our employees and partners are familiar with our security policy and practices. Your personal information is only accessible to a limited number of qualified people who are given a password in order to gain access to the information. While we take commercially reasonable measures to maintain a secure site, electric communications and databases are subject to errors, tampering and break-ins, and we cannot guarantee or warrant that such events will not take place and we will not be liable for any such occurrences. You will find that almost all Internet e-commerce providers make this same claim, especially if they use privacy policy templates such as this one to make known their company or organization's privacy policies.

### Are Children Allowed to Use Volcanoecigs.com?

No! Our products are only sold to adult smokers, 18 years or older. Volcanoecigs.com does not intentionally collect or solicit personal information from or about children or anyone under the age of 18. If we discover we have received any information from an individual under the age of 18 and in violation of this Policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe Volcanoecigs.com has any information from or about anyone under the age of 18, please [contact us](http://www.volcanoecigs.com/index.php/contacts%3Econtact%20us%3C/a%3E.%3C/p%3E%20%20%3Ch3%3EConditions%20of%20Use,%20Notices,%20and%20Revisions%20%3C/h3%3E%20%3Cp%3EIf%20you%20choose%20to%20visit%20Volcanoecigs.com,%20your%20visit%20and%20any%20dispute%20over%20privacy%20is%20subject%20to%20this%20Notice%20and%20our%20Conditions%20of%20Use,%20including%20limitations%20on%20damages,%20arbitration%20of%20disputes,%20and%20application%20of%20the%20laws%20of%20the%20State%20of%20Hawaii.%20If%20you%20have%20any%20concern%20about%20privacy%20at%20Volcanoecigs.com,%20please%20%3Ca%20href=) with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Because our business changes constantly, our Privacy Policy and the Conditions of Use will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web Site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.
